(This story is entirely fictional)
Let's go get fried chicken.
Coming or not?
No, it's too greasy.
Why?
Too greasy.
Yesterday, you promised
to go with me today.
A new squid place opened up.
Let's go eat.
(Norwegian Wood by Haruki Murakami)
(Based on the novel
Doctor Qin: Executer)
You wrote this?
(Math problem)
Can't you solve it,
or are you testing me?
I... I can't solve it.
I expected your help.
You're okay at taking photos.
Lying isn't your strong suit.
=Doctor Qin: Executer=
=Episode 19=
After that day,
I understood.
All her reckoning
was because
she'd suffered pain
I could never imagine.
I don't know how long it was,
but one day,
she came back.
It's all over.
Today is the anniversary
of my dad's death.
He jumped from a building.
I did one wrong thing.
To cover it up,
I did more wrong things.
Then I did many, many even worse things
to cover it up.
Tell me,
am I even worse
than the people
I killed?
Why am I telling you all this?
I know you've been painting me.
Why do you paint me?
Because...
you're beautiful.
Your...
eyes...
hold stories.
Am I pretty?
I don't remember what I look like.
For these twenty-some years,
I've never really looked at myself.
Only two guys
once took photos of me.
It was in a field of sunflowers.
Can you paint another portrait of me?
A portrait with eyes.
And a smile.
Is that okay?
Let's stop here.
She told me
she didn't want to kill me.
I didn't do anything wrong.
But I saw everything
and painted it.
So I have to die.
Ms. Zhang?
Ms. Zhang, what's wrong?
Zhang Lanfen?
You're safe now.
Tell me,
where is she now?
She...
She's dead!
Dead?
How did she die?
Where's the body?
Zhang Lanfen?
Dead...
Go get a doctor!
Got it!
They're all dead!
Zhang Lanfen?
All dead...
(Qin,)
(Zhang Lanfen says
Jin Keke is already dead.)
(Qin, did you hear that?)
Impossible.
Where's the body? How did she die?
(Zhang Lanfen is extremely emotional.)
(She won't say anything.)
(We suspect that...)
You suspect
Zhang Lanfen killed her?
(Dr. Qin,)
(we found blood spots
on Zhang Lanfen's clothes.)
(DNA test says it's Jin Keke's.)
All dead!
All dead...
Zhang Lanfen?
(Want to save her? Come alone
to the abandoned water plant!)
(Remember, you're not a cop for now!)
(If you call the police,
you'll never see your lost love again!)
Dead?
Where's the body?
We have to get Zhang Lanfen to talk.
We suspect she killed Jin Keke.
She fakes illness to stall for time.
Chief.
There's rust
in Zhang Lanfen's fingernails.
Sunflower pollen in her hair.
Different cat hairs on her clothes.
Rust.
Pollen.
Cat hair.
Zhang Lanfen was held
in Su Shi's cat shelter!
What are you waiting for?
Get moving!
Yes, sir!
(Police)
(FAN A8028 Police)
Move in!
Mr. Han, no one here!
No one here!
Report: no one here!
(Liang, we've got something.)
(Song Yalan talked to Jin Keke.)
Let's go! Song Yalan's place!
(Mom, I miss you.)
(How have you been?)
(Keke,)
(are you doing something dangerous?)
(The police visited our house.)
(Are you okay?)
(I can't come back for a while.)
(Can you bring me some clothes?)
(Mom, I miss you.)
(No power strips or chargers on the bed)
(How have you been?)
(Turn off water after washing veggies)
(Keke,)
(are you doing something dangerous?)
(The police visited our house.)
(Are you okay?)
(I can't come back for a while.)
(Zhang Xiaodong)
(Can you bring me some clothes?)
(If anything happens, contact Keke)
(Mom, I miss you.)
(Le Tianyi)
(How have you been?)
(Keke,)
(are you doing something dangerous?)
(The police visited our house.)
Remote control?
Han Liang.
Jin Keke is at the water plant
in Hailun District.
She's in danger.
Call for backup!
What's wrong?
Qin Ming says Jin Keke is in danger.
Isn't Jin Keke dead?
Qin Ming called?
It really was Qin Ming.
(FAN A 95T79)
Keke?
(Qin Ming, you're finally here.)
(Did you find the Executer?)
(Do you know the truth?)
(Or is it just
your self-righteous truth?)
(Today you'll find
the answer to the puzzle.)
(However,)
(you'll also have to pay the price.)
(Are you ready?)
(Welcome to the Executer's judgment.)
(Qin Ming!)
Keke?
Qin Ming!
It's dangerous here! Go now!
Go!
Don't come any closer! Go now!
Keke!
Qin Ming!
(Qin Ming,)
(beneath Jin Keke's feet
is a current leading to hell.)
(The voltage in the current
won't kill her right away.)
(Countless currents will pass
through her pores,)
(boring into every nerve in her body.)
(She'll endure the most extreme pain,)
(then slowly die in agony.)
Who are you?
Who on earth are you?
(Never mind who I am.)
(Jin Keke killed so many people.)
(She deserves a taste
of being killed herself.)
(Qin Ming,)
(see the gun hanging beside you?)
(You should know what it's for.)
(I suggest you decide quickly.)
(Either watch her be tortured to death,)
(or give her a quick death.)
(I'm waiting for your choice.)
(Qin Ming,)
(you were top three in marksmanship
at the police academy.)
(So I only gave you one bullet.)
(Shoot accurately.)
(Otherwise,)
(she'll suffer even more.)
Qin Ming!
Qin Ming,
I died ten years ago.
You still have a future.
Don't throw yourself away!
I'm sorry, Keke.
I won't let you hurt anymore.
Keke!
(You actually fired.)
(It was a blank.)
(Surprised? Unexpected?)
(Qin Ming, good performance.)
(However,)
(I can see you don't want her to die.)
(Then let's play another round.)
(Next,)
(we play for real.)
Keke!
Qin Ming!
(Qin Ming,)
(are you willing to trade your life...)
No!
(for Jin Keke's life?)
(You have five seconds to decide.)
Qin Ming!
Keke...
In the first letter I wrote you,
the answer to that problem
was my message to you.
(Given the perimeter of △PF₁F₂ is 10,)
(with fixed points F₁(–c,0), F₂(c,0),
and point P(x,y) where |PF₁|+|PF₂|=10,)
(Find P's path equation c.
If c is tangent to y=x+b, find b.)
(|PF₁|...)
♪Wind through blooms, waves of gold♪
♪Chalk dust falls on white uniforms♪
♪You turned and took the summer away♪
Qin Ming!
♪Leaving an unsolved ellipse equation♪
♪Sunset washes over the old wall♪
♪Milk tea cools on the stone steps♪
♪Sea wind tugs at your sleeve♪
♪Unspoken words just flee and fade♪
♪The marks on the desk
have faded yellow♪
♪I turned around,
and a gunshot rang out♪
♪No one can truly feel another's pain♪
♪The wind is cold,
a fading shadow sways♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪A bullet pierces the spring night♪
♪You sink into the vast crowd♪
♪Years later, when we meet again♪
♪Don't mention this moonlit night♪
♪The waves smooth
two lines of footprints♪
♪Half a cup of sweetness
sinks into the sand♪
♪Tonight, I don't care
about the universe♪
♪I only want to see this through
with you♪
♪Wind back to shore,
clouds back to hills♪
♪We stop here in this night♪
♪This is the past, the only,
the last look back♪
♪One gunshot echoes through half a life♪